jumpmanual.com 2011-11-04

# The Jump Manual Privacy Policy | The Jump Manual: Comprehensive vertical jump training manual. How to jump higher.

**The Jump Manual Privacy Notice**  
Effective 04/02/2009 

**Privacy Notice Table Of Contents:**  
• Our Commitment To Privacy  
• The Information We Collect  
• How We Use Information  
• Our Commitment To Data Security  
• How To Access Or Correct Your Information  
• How To Contact Us

**Our Commitment To Privacy:** Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

**The Information We Collect:**  
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on The Jump Manual website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

Name  
Address  
Email address 

* For purchases we use Clickbank, a third party secure merchant service so your data is 100% secure. See below for details.

**The Way We Use Information:**  
We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive and to ship the e-product. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. You can register with our website if you would like to receive our newsletter as well as updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form. We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

**Our Commitment To Data Security**  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We use a third party, ClickBank, an online retail outlet with over 10,000 digital product vendors, to handle all monetary transactions. This is carefully and responsibly regulated. You can read ClickBank’s privacy policy here. 

**How You Can Correct Your Information**  
To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

**How To Contact Us**  
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send an email to jacobATjacobhiller.com. 

________________________________________
